<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web Development on JOANNE</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/</link><description>Recent content in Web Development on JOANNE</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:57:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Ace the AWS Certified Developer Exam in 2024: A Step-by-Step Guide</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/aws/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Feb 2024 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/aws/</guid><description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s cloud-driven world, AWS has become the go-to platform for developers. With its wide range of services, from compute and storage to networking and databases, AWS offers everything you need to build and deploy scalable, reliable applications.
If you&amp;rsquo;re a developer looking to boost your career, earning the AWS Certified Developer certification is a great place to start. This industry-recognized credential validates your skills and knowledge in AWS, giving you a competitive edge in the job market.</description></item><item><title>Hugo - basic commands and hosting</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/static-site-generator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/static-site-generator/</guid><description>As a software engineer, my friends often approach me with requests like, &amp;ldquo;I need a personal website to showcase my projects. Do you know how to create one?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Can you build a website for my product?&amp;rdquo; Having a dedicated website can significantly enhance the professional image of a person or their product. If you share the same need, you might want to consider using a static site generator to build your website.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting for Firefox showing error while downloading .xlsx file</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/firefox-mime/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/firefox-mime/</guid><description>While downloading the excel file in firefox, it shows a message box of &amp;lsquo;What should Firefox do with this file?&amp;rsquo;, giving options are open or save the file, if choose to open it, firefox opens it as &amp;lsquo;file.xlsx.xls&amp;rsquo; and the error comes up: The file format and extension of &amp;lsquo;filename.xlsx.xls&amp;rsquo; don&amp;rsquo;t match. The file could be corrupted or unsafe. Unless you trust its source, don&amp;rsquo;t open it. Do you want to open it anyway?</description></item><item><title>Common Cross Site Scripting(XSS) and ways to prevent it</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/cross-site-scripting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/cross-site-scripting/</guid><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) is a client-side code injection attack. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the most commonly seen website attacks, even Facebook and Google has been exposed having XSS vulnerabilities.
If successful, XSS vulnerabilities can be exploited to manipulate or steal cookies, create requests that can be mistaken for those of a valid user, compromise confidential information, or execute malicious code on end-user systems.
As a web developer, it&amp;rsquo;s better to know how it works and avoid using those codes than to revise the project after the vulnerabilities being detected or targeted.</description></item></channel></rss>