<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web Development on Anchiao</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/</link><description>Recent content in Web Development on Anchiao</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:57:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Troubleshooting for Firefox showing error while downloading .xlsx file</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/firefox-mime/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/firefox-mime/</guid><description>While downloading the excel file in firefox, it shows a message box of &amp;lsquo;What should Firefox do with this file?&amp;rsquo;, giving options are open or save the file, if choose to open it, firefox opens it as &amp;lsquo;file.xlsx.xls&amp;rsquo; and the error comes up: The file format and extension of &amp;lsquo;filename.xlsx.xls&amp;rsquo; don&amp;rsquo;t match. The file could be corrupted or unsafe. Unless you trust its source, don&amp;rsquo;t open it. Do you want to open it anyway?</description></item><item><title>Common Cross Site Scripting(XSS) and ways to prevent it</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/cross-site-scripting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/cross-site-scripting/</guid><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) is a client-side code injection attack. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the most commonly seen website attacks, even Facebook and Google has been exposed having XSS vulnerabilities.
If successful, XSS vulnerabilities can be exploited to manipulate or steal cookies, create requests that can be mistaken for those of a valid user, compromise confidential information, or execute malicious code on end-user systems.
As a web developer, it&amp;rsquo;s better to know how it works and avoid using those codes than to revise the project after the vulnerabilities being detected or targeted.</description></item></channel></rss>