<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on JOANNE</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on JOANNE</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 10:57:25 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://anchiao.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hugo - basic commands and hosting</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/static-site-generator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/static-site-generator/</guid><description>As a software engineer, my friends often approach me with requests like, &amp;ldquo;I need a personal website to showcase my projects. Do you know how to create one?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Can you build a website for my product?&amp;rdquo; Having a dedicated website can significantly enhance the professional image of a person or their product. If you share the same need, you might want to consider using a static site generator to build your website.</description></item><item><title>Get Most Visited</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/java/codingtest/getmostvisited/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/java/codingtest/getmostvisited/</guid><description>Task description: Pat is an ordinary kid who works hard to be a great runner. As part of training, Pat must run sprints of different intervals on a straight trail. The trail has numbered markers that the coach uses as goals. Pat&amp;rsquo;s coach provides a list of goals to reach in order. Each time Pat starts at, stops at, or passes a marker it is considered a visit. Determine the lowest numbered marker that is visited the most times during Pat&amp;rsquo;s day of training.</description></item><item><title>ParkingBill</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/java/codingtest/parkingbill/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/java/codingtest/parkingbill/</guid><description>Codility test ParkingBill
Task description:
You parked your car in a parking lot and want to compute the total cost of the ticket. The billing rules are as follows:
The entrance fee of the car parking lot is 2; The first full or partial hour costs 3; Each successive full or partial hour (after the first) costs 4. You entered the car parking lot at time E and left at time L.</description></item><item><title>Troubleshooting for Firefox showing error while downloading .xlsx file</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/firefox-mime/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/firefox-mime/</guid><description>While downloading the excel file in firefox, it shows a message box of &amp;lsquo;What should Firefox do with this file?&amp;rsquo;, giving options are open or save the file, if choose to open it, firefox opens it as &amp;lsquo;file.xlsx.xls&amp;rsquo; and the error comes up: The file format and extension of &amp;lsquo;filename.xlsx.xls&amp;rsquo; don&amp;rsquo;t match. The file could be corrupted or unsafe. Unless you trust its source, don&amp;rsquo;t open it. Do you want to open it anyway?</description></item><item><title>Common Cross Site Scripting(XSS) and ways to prevent it</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/cross-site-scripting/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 10:57:25 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/webdevelopment/cross-site-scripting/</guid><description>Cross-site Scripting (XSS) is a client-side code injection attack. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the most commonly seen website attacks, even Facebook and Google has been exposed having XSS vulnerabilities.
If successful, XSS vulnerabilities can be exploited to manipulate or steal cookies, create requests that can be mistaken for those of a valid user, compromise confidential information, or execute malicious code on end-user systems.
As a web developer, it&amp;rsquo;s better to know how it works and avoid using those codes than to revise the project after the vulnerabilities being detected or targeted.</description></item><item><title>Insert Large Data Manually To Avoid Timeout</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/sql/largedata/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/sql/largedata/</guid><description>As part of a batch project, I have to insert/update large data (up to millions rows) into a MSSQL database. This requires insert into a hundred rows in one statement, then looping through all datas, such long transaction may encounter an error of jta transaction unexpectedly rolled back (maybe due to a timeout). Here&amp;rsquo;s how to handle this exception.
Basic setting The transaction annotation timeout value, can be set up to Integer.</description></item><item><title>Upload and Download File by SFTP</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/java/ftp/uploadanddownloadfilebysftp/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2021 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/java/ftp/uploadanddownloadfilebysftp/</guid><description>When data is sent to another party, it&amp;rsquo;s potentially exposed to outside entities on the Internet, FTP and SFTP are two common file transfer options, Learning more about them will make a proper choice for sharing your company’s data.
FTP v.s SFTP FTP is file transfer protocol. It&amp;rsquo;s a simple way of transferring data, making data readable for anyone who intercepts it. While this is fine if you’re just sending unimportant files.</description></item><item><title>MSSQL temporary table</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/sql/mssql/temp-table/</link><pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/sql/mssql/temp-table/</guid><description>Temporary tables are used to store data temporarily and they can perform CRUD (Create, Read, Update, and Delete), join, and some other operations like the persistent database tables, which gives us more flexibility to get the info we want from the database. SQL Server supports a few types of temporary tables by using #, ## or @ before the table name, they exist for a different session.
1.Using #TempTable a single hashtag (#) sign before the table name indicates a local temporary table, it&amp;rsquo;s available ONLY to the session that created it and is dropped when the session is closed, use it when you need the table to be visible only in the current session.</description></item><item><title>How to solve Homebrew installation failure?</title><link>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/macos-directory/homebrew/homebrew-installation/</link><pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2021 08:06:25 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://anchiao.github.io/posts/macos-directory/homebrew/homebrew-installation/</guid><description>If you got this error message while installing Homebrew on macOS, follow my steps for troubleshooting!
The operation couldn’t be completed. (NSURLErrorDomain error -1012.) ==&amp;gt; Installing the Command Line Tools (expect a GUI popup): ==&amp;gt; /usr/bin/sudo /usr/bin/xcode-select --install xcode-select: note: install requested for command line developer tools Press any key when the installation has completed. ==&amp;gt; /usr/bin/sudo /usr/bin/xcode-select --switch /Library/Developer/CommandLineTools xcode-select: error: invalid developer directory &amp;#39;/Library/Developer/CommandLineTools&amp;#39; Failed during: /usr/bin/sudo /usr/bin/xcode-select --switch /Library/Developer/CommandLineTools Download CommandLine Tools Command Line Tools is the basic requirements for downloading homebrew, if you haven&amp;rsquo;t got one, simply download it manually on Apple Developer</description></item></channel></rss>